edge.ca 2019-12-09

# Privacy Policy - Corus Entertainment

Last updated: March 6, 2018

Corus Entertainment Inc. and its affiliates understand and appreciate the concerns that you may have with regard to personal information gathered on our Sites. Corus has adopted this Privacy Policy to provide transparency to you and to ensure the confidentiality of such personal information. Corus has a separate privacy policy for our Corus Kids Sites, please refer to the Corus Kids Privacy Policy if you are on one of the Corus Kids Sites.

## INTRODUCTION

We respect your privacy and believe the best way to serve you through a Site is with honesty, accountability and adherence to legal standards. We are extremely sensitive to the issue of privacy and have structured the features of Corus’ Sites to minimize the requirement to collect personal information, and to maximize your control over the collection, use and disclosure of any personal information.

By visiting or interacting with our Sites, you agree to be bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy. We may change this Privacy Policy at any time, and your continued use of our Sites indicates your agreement to the revised terms. Accordingly, you should review this Privacy Policy from time to time to keep informed of such amendments. The most recent date of revision will be indicated prominently at the top of the Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy applies to the Sites where this Privacy Policy is posted, and does not apply to other Sites operated by Corus or third parties. Please read the respective Sites’ terms of use and policies when accessing such other sites or using such third party applications.

Please also make sure to read Corus’ Terms of Use as it supplements and forms part of this Privacy Policy. By using the Site you are agreeing to be bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy and Terms of Use. If you do not agree to the terms of this policy or any revised Privacy Policy, please do not register as a user or further interact with the Site.

## PRIVACY OF CHILDREN

We encourage parents and guardian to be aware of and participate in their Children’s online activities. Minors (persons under the age of majority in their province or territory of residence) may not use the Site unsupervised and we ask that you do not allow your child to submit any personal information to us. We do not knowingly collect the personal information of minors or Children. If you believe your child has provided personal information, please contact Corus’ Privacy Office at [privacy@corusent.com and we will delete it](mailto:privacy@corusent.com). Parents are requested to review this Privacy Policy and discuss its main features with their children, in a manner that the child will understand.

For more information regarding marketing to children, please visit the [Canadian Marketing Association’s Special Considerations in Marketing to Children guidelines](https://www.the-cma.org/regulatory/code-of-ethics), Section K of the CMA’s Code of Ethics and Standards of Practice.

There are software programs that allow parents to block certain websites from their kids. Some programs are more flexible than others, so you may want to shop around to find one that you’re comfortable with.

## WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?

We may collect two types of information from visitors to the Sites: Personal Information and Non-Personal Information. The website will collect Personal Information with consent or only where it is voluntarily provided by the individual.

Non-Personal Information is any information that cannot be associated with an identifiable individual, such as aggregated statistical information (e.g. the average length of time users spend visiting the site), or other anonymous information, such as the type and version of browser being used to access the website or application. Your computer and its operating systems, browsers, and memory contain vast quantities of transaction data and records of your use of it.

We may also collect information about you from a social network site you may be a member of or have connected from, in order to provide you with a more personalized experience. In some cases, we will collect psychographic data from third parties that help us better understand our users.

If you send an e-mail to us, or fill out our “feedback” form through the Site, we will collect your e-mail address and the full content of your e-mail, including attached files, and other information you provide. We may use and display your full name and email address when you send an email notification to a friend through the Site or the social network from which you have connected to the website or application (such as in an invitation, or when sharing your content).

## PERSONAL INFORMATION REQUIRED FOR CONTESTS

You may be able to enter a contest through the Site. If you are 13 years of age and under, we require the consent of a Parent prior to the submission of your personal information. On the online entry form, we ask for personal information such as the entrant’s name and address. Unless otherwise specified in the applicable contest rules, this personal information is collected, used and/or disclosed solely for the purpose of awarding contest prizes, tracking compliance with the official rules and regulations and for internal feedback purposes. We will only use and disclose a contest winner’s name and photograph after receiving prior written consent from the winner (or their Parent, if the winner is under the age of majority in his or her Province of residence) and the appropriate release forms are fully completed and returned to us.

## WHAT ARE YOUR CHOICES?

We do not sell or otherwise share Personal Information about individual users without the prior approval of the user. On the page where we ask for that information, there is a prominently displayed method to indicate to us that you do or do not want to receive promotional and/or marketing information about products, services and offerings. Its always your choice, if you choose not to receive promotional and/or marketing information we consider it an opt-out. User consent to use Personal Information can be withdrawn at any time by unsubscribing in the manner provided on each piece of promotion and/or marketing information we send to you or by emailing our Privacy Officer at [privacy@corusent.com](mailto:privacy@corusent.com).  

## WHAT ARE COOKIES AND HOW ARE THEY USED?

Cookies are small data files that your browser may place on your computer when you visit different websites to mark that you have been there. Cookies and other technologies, such as your device’s unique identifier, are used on our website to maximize the website-browsing experience. For example, they allow us to track a browser’s movement through the website over several sessions. Through these technologies, the website can recognize repeat visitors, facilitate the visitor’s access to and use of the website and allows the website to track usage behaviour that will allow content and service improvement and enable us to tailor our website and advertising to better match your interests and preferences. We may also use these technologies to allow you to select and prioritize your preferences when you enter our Site.

No Personal Information is stored in or gathered from these cookies or other technology. However, you may choose to set up your browser to delete and/or refuse cookies or alert you when cookies are sent. Please note, though, if you don’t have a cookie from our Site, it may limit our ability to customize and improve our Site features.  

## WHY IS THE INFORMATION COLLECTED?

We may collect your Personal Information in order to enable us to make general improvements to the Site, ensure that content standards of the website or application are rigorously upheld, enable us to contact you (for example, registration is needed to enter certain contests) and better serve your specific interests. You may choose not to provide your personal information, but this may lead to decreased functionality of the Site for you and will prevent us from providing you with certain products or services. However, you can still access and visit many of the website’s features. We may also request you to voluntarily provide personal information that is not required to access features of our website.

For example, we may collect information from you to allow you to:

• Join a club or become a member;  
• Enter a contest or other promotion;  
• Subscribe to our e-mail newsletter(s);  
• Respond to online questionnaires;  
• To participate in interactive online activities (such as games, chatrooms or bulletin boards);  
• To shop online at our and/or our contractor’s website; or  
• To contact us to make requests or comment on our services.

In addition to using Personal Information to keep in contact with users we may use your information for the following purposes: (i) to better understand viewer and user needs and preferences; (ii) to improve the content and format of our Sites; (iii) to notify visitors about updates to our Sites; (iv) to keep you informed and market products and services (both ours and third parties’);(v) to administer contests and special events; (vi) to establish your eligibility for special offers and discounts; (vii) to complete business transactions; (viii) to contact you as part of a promotion; (ix) to administer individual accounts; (x) to provide customer support; (xi) to personalize your experience and make content recommendations; and (xi) to meet legal requirements.

Non-Personal information is used to assess general usage patterns, including identifying repeat users, collect demographic information, for research and analytical purposes, to provide advertisements about goods and services of possible interest to you, to administer and make improvements to the Sites to tailor our visitor’s experiences at the Site and display content according to their preferences so as to make it more useful to you and other users. We, including our affiliates and such other third party as we may designate reserve the right to use, maintain, update, disclose and/or sell anonymous, aggregated information to third parties.

We may transparently collect or may use third-party advertising and analytics companies to collect Non-Personal Information and/or serve ads to users when they visit our Sites, as well as other website and offline activity through the use of Cookies or similar technologies.

If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, visit [youradchoices.ca](https://youradchoices.ca/). Rest assured that we nor any third parties acting on our behalf collect browsing information respecting the use of the site by children, nor do we target advertising to children based on browsing activity.

We may also infer information about you based on the information you provide to us or information we receive from third parties, including information we may receive from social media sites, in accordance with your privacy settings on such Sites. We may also collect demographic, psychographic and lifestyle profile data from third parties, which may be predictively associated with you, based on what we know about you. For example, data may be available suggesting common interests or attributes of people living in your postal district. Any such information that is considered to be Personal Information, will be treated as such according to this Privacy Policy. If you would prefer that we not associate such third party data with you, you may opt-out by visiting <http://youradchoices.ca/choices>.

AppChoices gives you transparency with more than 30 participating companies (and counting), and lets you limit their collection of cross-app data for interest-based ads. Brought to you by the Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada, and backed up by the DAAC’s independent accountability program, AppChoices lets you opt out from interest-based advertising with a particular company, or “Choose All Companies” with one simple click. Download AppChoices on your mobile device here: <http://youradchoices.com/appchoices>  

## WITH WHOM DO WE SHARE INFORMATION?

We work closely with a number of parties who may perform functions on our behalf, including fulfilling orders, providing streaming services or other third party content, providing promotional materials to our users, sending e-mail, managing, compiling and processing data, administering contests, processing credit card payments or providing customer service. Data, including Personal Information, may be stored or processed outside Canada or in the cloud where it will be subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which it resides. We do not disclose your Personal Information to these parties except to the extent necessary to enable them to provide the specific services to you or on your behalf. Third party service providers are contractually bound to maintain the confidentiality of your Personal Information and are prohibited from using your Personal Information for any other purpose.

Other than for the specific purposes set forth in this Privacy Policy, we will not disclose your Personal Information to any third parties unless we obtain your prior consent or are legally compelled to do so or to protect and defend our rights or property. In addition, we will not contact you without your permission except as specified above or in connection with the registration process.

In the event of a proposed or actual sale of all or a substantial portion of our business assets, your Personal Information may be disclosed to potential buyers where necessary to determine whether to proceed with the transaction. Where such a transaction is completed, your Personal Information may be among the transferred assets. In such event, the purchaser will continue to be subject to the confidentiality obligations posted herein.

## SMS NOTIFICATIONS; PUSH NOTIFICATIONS

If we offer SMS notification or push notification functionality, and you choose to receive SMS notifications and/or push notifications, we may send such notifications to your mobile device. We will collect and store the information you provide, including your telephone number. You can opt out of receiving SMS and push notifications and you can adjust the types of notifications you receive, and when you receive them, by editing your notification settings on your mobile device. You can also opt out of receiving SMS and push notifications by emailing. We will not charge a fee to use SMS notifications or push notifications, but any text messages sent and/or received are subject to standard text messaging rates. Additionally, text messages sent and/or received count towards a monthly quota as any other messages do. Any users, whether sending or receiving text messages, should be aware that standard text messaging rates may apply. Text messaging rates can normally be found by asking your mobile carrier.

## SHOW/CONTENT SUBMISSION

Occasionally, you will have the opportunity to submit ideas or content such as videos or audio for inclusion on the Site for airing on one of our services. At the time of submission, the producers of these shows will also ask the users to include a contact number, email or address. Only those who produce the show in question will have access to the contact information and it will not be passed on to a third party. People who submit ideas or content may be contacted if the show’s producers are possibly interested in using such submissions.

## ABOUT OUR FORUMS

The Site may, from time-to-time, feature forums (such as message boards and chat rooms) which enable our users to communicate with each other. We do not moderate and are not responsible for the content that you or any user posts on any forum on the Site. All Personal Information you post in a forum becomes public information and may be viewed, collected and used by any visitor to the Site, and may expose you to unsolicited messages. This is beyond our control. Therefore, we strongly recommend that you do not post, on any forum, private information about yourself or other individuals.

## LINKING TO OUR BUSINESS PARTNERS’ AND THIRD PARTY CONTENT/WEBSITES

Please keep in mind that this Privacy Policy applies to the Site only. The Site may provide on-line media streaming and other third party content. Occasionally, the Site may contain links from and to sites operated by other Corus companies, our business partners and other independent third parties whose privacy practices may be different from ours. Once you leave the Site, you may or may not see a new URL in the location bar. If you submit Personal Information to any of those sites, your information is governed by the privacy policies of those destination websites. Please review the linked website’s and third party content provider’s privacy policies, and do not use or further visit these sites if you do not agree with the terms of these policies. The linked websites are not under our influence or control, and we are not responsible for the privacy policies and practices or the content of the websites operated by our business partners or other third parties or the privacy policies and practices or contents of any linked site or subsequent links from that website.

This Site may include social media features, like the Facebook “Like” button or may also permit you to link to other social media websites on the Internet (e.g., Twitter, Facebook, Pinterest, Tumblr, among others) (“Social Media Sites”). By accessing the website through a Social Media Site, mobile device or other third party platform or service or by connecting to such a platform or service via the website, these features may collect information about your IP address and which page you are visiting, and may set a Cookie or we may be authorized to collect, store, and use personal information as permitted by your user agreement and your settings with such Social Media Site, mobile device or other third party platform. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with those features are governed by the privacy policies of the companies that provide them.

## ”REFER A FRIEND” OR “SHARING” FEATURES

If you choose to use a referral service to “tell a friend” about the website, a specific article or feature on the website, or a contest that is running, we may ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will then send your friend an email on your behalf inviting him or her to visit the relevant webpage or check out the website. We store your friend’s name and email for a short period for the sole purpose of sending this email and for redundancy checking, to be sure that your friend does not receive multiple copies of the same email message. We do not keep or use this information for any other purpose.  

## HOW WE PROTECT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We have policies and procedures in place to protect the integrity, privacy and confidentiality of the information that we collect and maintain, including contracts with third parties that manage the information provided by you. All Personal Information is stored on secure servers, behind a firewall at a data center with strictly controlled access. Please be aware that, despite our best efforts, no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. We review our security procedures on a regular basis to consider new technology methods. Only individuals specifically involved in the analysis and other functions set out herein have access to your Personal Information. These individuals have been provided the requisite training on our privacy policies and practices.

To help ensure the privacy of your information, we urge you not to share your user name and password with anyone and recommend that you change your password frequently and store it in a safe place. If you are asked to create a user name or password, please select words that do not personally identify you. We may offer “auto login” which allows users to enter member areas of our website without re-entering password information. You may want to disable auto login on your device, in order to prevent access by unauthorized users of your device.

## UPDATING/DELETING YOUR INFORMATION

Your Personal Information will be kept as reasonably necessary for the intended purpose or as required by law. Once your Personal Information is no longer necessary or is required by law to be no longer retained, your Personal Information will be destroyed or de-identified.

Users of the Site may delete any Personal Information previously submitted through the Site, unless such deletion would compromise privacy or security interests. To update or delete your information, please contact the company’s Privacy Officer, at the address listed below.

## DEFINITIONS

Corus Entertainment Inc. and its subsidiaries (“Corus”) refer to all of the companies owned and/or controlled by Corus. These companies operate under a number of brands, which include, among others, the following:

Corus Kids: refer to the Corus’ kids focused brands, which include, among others, the following:

Personal Information is any information about you as an identifiable individual, such as your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, age, marital status, education level, intentions, preferences and opinions. We only collect Personal Information where you voluntarily provide it.

Non-Personal Information is any information that cannot be associated with an identifiable individual, such as aggregated statistical information (e.g. the average length of time you spend visiting the website), or other anonymous information, such as the type and version of browser being used to access the website. Your computer and its operating systems, browsers, and memory contain vast quantities of transaction data and records of your use of it.

Sites include all websites and Applications owned and/or controlled by Corus.

An Application or App is a program designed to perform a specific function directly for the user, which may be displayed online, on mobile or other platforms.

Children are individuals who are not of legal age to provide consent for the collection of their personal information, which includes persons 13 years of age or younger.

## QUESTIONS/CONCERNS?

If you have any concerns about privacy procedures respecting our websites or applications, or to find out further details about how your Personal Information may be used, write us at:

Corus Entertainment Inc.  
Corus Quay, 25 Dockside Drive,  
Toronto, Ontario M5A 0B5  
Attn: Chief Privacy Officer

Or you may email us at [privacy@corusent.com](mailto:privacy@corusent.com).

Please make any communications as complete and descriptive as possible, and we will attempt to respond promptly to your concerns.

### Office of the Privacy Commissioner of Canada

The Office of the Privacy Commissioner of Canada oversees our Personal Information handling practices. If any privacy concerns are not addressed to your satisfaction you may contact the Office of the Privacy Commissioner of Canada for further guidance:

By Phone:  1-800-282-1376 or 819-994-5444

By Fax:          819-994-6591

Website:     [www.priv.gc.ca](http://www.priv.gc.ca/)

© 2017 Corus Entertainment Inc.
